FRANKLIN PETERS

PROGRAMMER AT TRC

☑gagewaguespack@gmail.com ८ (985)-718-7763 🕻 Gage-Waguespack

SUMMARY

Game Programmer with 3+ years of experience! I know how to program in C++, C#, Unity, and Unreal Engine. Looking to expand my programming knowledge and gain more experience in the field working on just about any project. Great team member and very flexible with hours, pay, and type of work.

EDUCATION

Slidell High School Jan. 2016 - June 2018

St. James High School Aug. 2018 - June 2020

High School Graduate 2020

I transferred from Slidell High to St. James in 2018.

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Associates of Occupational Studies and Game Programming 2022

EMPLOYMENT

TRC, *Programmer*, Home

Dec. 2022 - Current

Aug. 2020 - June 2022

Programmer, App and Game Tester, and also worked with feedback to update apps.

Chick-Fil-A, *Staff Member*, Lafayette, LA

Sept. 2021 - Dec. 2022

Worked both in the kitchen and with the customers.

Olive Garden, Busser, Lafayette, LA

2020 - 2021

Cleaned Tables and occasionally assisted customers as well as stocked and refilled soda machines, tea, and coffee.

SKILLS

GAME PROGRAMMING: C++, C#, Markdown

TEAM WORK: Training others at CFA, Working with others on company projects.

SOFTWARE AND TOOLS: Microsoft Visual Studios, Unreal Engine, Unity, Git, Perforce, Trello, Plastic

PROJECTS

Item Generation

Spring 2021 - Jan. 2022

A project with a complex game system that allows you to randomly generate weapons! (can be used in bigger projects)

Stratus Jan. 2022 - June 2022

Our major production project at AIE in which we made, pitched, and produced a game to Itch.io with trailers and documentation!